This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Initial
Raise up your hands takaku
Raise up your hands 高く[Everybody gonna tell you I can't stop]
(Everybody now te wo agero saa)
Tsukame brand new tomorrow
掴め Brand new tomorrow[You don't stop]
(You don't stop)
Kaze no naka de jibun wo shiru
風の中で 自分を知る ずっと最高のDreamだろう
Zutto zekkei no dream darou
(Let's go)
Oh[Let's go] Oh[Let's go]
Oh
Oh (Let's go)
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Oh raise up you can't stop
Ikiteru dake de marumouke nara ganbarouze marugoto ittennbari
生きてるだけで何やろうかな
Gamble on 迫る鼓動にテンバリ
Onaji mission, onaji isshou
同じMission 同じ一生
Dondake yume atsuika ga shobu darou
どんだけ夢熱いかが勝負だろ
Escalator nashi no eien
Escalator 無しの永遠
Ashi koshi kitae reruze yeah, yeah
足腰鍛え Let's begin yeah
Douse noboru kaidan
どうせのぼる階段
Kokoro kocchi ni customize shichaeba ii
心こっちにCustomizeしちゃえばいい
Kezurarete sugiru mainichi
削られて 過ぎる毎日[But you know]
Kezurarete sugiru mainichi (But you know ?)
Semegai no aru game to warai tobashite
攻めがいのあるGameと 笑い飛ばして
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Let's see how fast you can do it
Raise up your hands zutto
Raise up your hands ずっと[Everybody gonna tell you I can't stop]
(Everybody now te wo agero saa)
Hashire sleepless challenger
走れ Sleepless challenger [You don't stop]
(You don't stop)
Ima ni ikiru riyuu sagasu
今に生きる 理由を探す
Yume tsukinai quest
夢尽きないQuest
(Let's go)
Oh[Let's go] Oh[Let's go]
Oh
Oh (Let's go)
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Oh raise up you can't stop
始まったかな
Has it begun ?
I don't know why,
but I've got goose bumps.
なんか知らないけど 急に鳥肌立ってる
スープラちゅう車はなんだかんだ言うてもグランツーリスモなんですわ
The Supra is a grand touring car, after all.
一般的にはレーシなイメージがありますけど
Generally speaking, it gives
off a race-oriented feel...
FDみたいな本気なスポーツカーとは方向性が違うと言いますか
...but its design approach is different
from a hardcore sports car like the FD.
ネックは重さでしょうな
Its weakness is its weight.
What you're trying to say is...
久保さんの言いたい事は つまり FDとスープラは峠で競争すれば
...when the FD and the Supra go head to head
in a mountain pass, the Supra will be inadequate.
スープラが不利だと
ということはドライバーの技量が限りなく接近した物になっていけば
So if the drivers' skills are very close, it's
possible for an amateur to embarrass a pro.
プロとアマの下剋上は在り得るって訳だ
それがこのバトルの核心でっしゃろ
That's the highlight of this battle.
離れる訳でもなく くっついてくる訳でもない
He isn't falling behind, but
isn't gaining on me, either.
それが気に入らない
I don't like that.
It really pisses me off.
すんげー嫌な感じだぜ
Keisuke's Pride
ほー 予想以上のペースですな
Their pace is much faster than expected.
I didn't expect them to be that fast.
まさか これ程とは思いませんでした
Since the race so far has
been a high speed match...
ここまでのスピード勝負になってくると
...the physical condition of the
tires will determine the outcome.
ラストは物理的なタイヤで決着する事になる
逃げるFDのドライバーは追い詰められてるでしょうが
The driver of the lead
FD must feel pressured...
本間に苦しいのは皆川の方でしょう
...but Minagawa is the one
who's actually hard-pressed.
I don't think he expected
the pace to be this fast.
これ程ペースが上がるとは思ってなかったはずや
この均衡は皆川が仕掛ける起死回生の心理戦ですな
The current deadlock must be Minagawa's
psychological attack for turning the situation around.
同時に皆川が切る事できる最後のカード
At the same time, it's the
last card Minagawa can deal.
くそー
Dammit.
我慢できるかできへんか
Victory hinges on whether the
lead driver can endure it or not.
勝敗の分岐点はそれ一点に絞られたっちゅうわけや
気のせいじゃねぇな
It's not my imagination,
he's slowly gaining on me.
ジリジリと来てる
必死で持ち堪えていた車間がジリジリと詰り始めている
The advantage I created
is narrowing bit by bit.
恐ろしいぜ 兄貴
The guy behind me is
pretty frightening, Brother.
後から来るこいつが
I feel like he's got one
more gear left to use.
ここまで来て更にもう一個上のギヤが残ってんのかよ
すげーなレーシングドライバーって
Race car drivers are so incredible
and scary, that they give me the chills.
ゾッとする程恐ろしい
頼んだぜFD
I'm counting on you, FD.
Your remaining strength is all I've got.
あとはお前の踏ん張りが俺の全てだ
ゴールはすぐそこなんだ
The goal is so close.
慌てるな啓介
Don't get in a hurry, Keisuke.
敵は死に物狂いでプレーシャを掛けてくるだろう
Your opponent will put
incredible pressure on you.
感情的になってそれがドライビングを狂わせたら
Emotions mess up one's driving,
which can easily reverse the situation.
情勢は簡単に引っ繰り返る
自分の車を信じて
Believe in your car, and
the experience you've gained.
そして積み重ねた経験を信じろ
成長の証を見せてみろ
Show the proof of your growth.
Step on the gas harder.
もっとアクセルを踏んでみろ
どうした もっと攻めろ
What's wrong ? Push harder.
もっとがむしゃらに死に物狂いで逃げてみろ
Try to get away...more desperately.
もっと もっと逃げるんだ
Harder ! Try harder to pull away !
逃げてくれ
Do it !
でないと この勝負 俺の負けだ
If you don't...
...I'll lose this battle.
タイヤの余力は全て使い切った
I used up all the potential of my tires.
I can't fight another round.
二本目を走る戦闘力はもうない
FDは車重の軽さとフロントミットエンジン故のバランスの良さが
The FD's superbly balanced lightweight body
and front-mid engine can reduce its tire wear.
タイヤの消耗を軽減してくれる
勝敗はそれで決まりでっしゃろ
That'll decide the winner and loser.
分かっていてもスピードの世界に生きる者としてのプライドを賭け
Knowing that, Minagawa still put up a fight for his
pride as a man who lives in the world of speed.
受けて立った皆川
それがこの区間レコードを大きく更新するハイペースを生んだんだ
The high-speed race that resulted broke
the course record by a big margin.
兄貴 やっぱりプロってすげーな
Brother, pros are really incredible.
そんな当たり前の事に今更気が付いたのか
You just realized something so obvious ?
More or less.
まあな
I have mixed feelings of joy and frustration.
俺嬉しさ半分悔しさ半分なんだ
I'm satisfied with myself for racing so well.
ここまで戦えた事に対しては自分でも満足してる
今の俺にできる事はやり尽くしたからな
I've done everything I can for now.
But I can't explain how I lost
my advantage right near the end.
だけど 終盤のあの追い詰められ方は
今の俺にはわからない未知の領域だった
少なくとも俺はめいいっぱい逃げていたし
At least, I did my best to pull away,
and I was able to manage that pace.
同じペースで走り続けていたのに
タイヤが苦しいのはどっちも同じはず
Both of us were struggling with worn tires, so
how did he pick up the pace in that situation ?
あの場面でペースアップできるってどういうことだろう
心底ゾッとしたよ
I was scared to death.
Do you know why, Brother ?
兄貴ならその理由分かるかな
相手がプロだぜ
Your opponent was a pro.
レーシングドライバーはスピードの限界ってやつを知り尽くしているからな
Racing drivers know everything
about speed at the limit.
積み重ねたキャリアの中でそれぞれが独自の引き出しを持っていて
Each driver has his own unique
technique they've learned from experience.
ここ一番の勝負所で更に一段限界を引き上げる術を知っている
They know how to raise the bar even
higher when the situation calls for it.
そのやり方はドライバー個々によって違うから
Every driver is different, so I
can't explain what Minagawa did...
皆川が何をしたのか 俺には説明できないけど
...but it probably has more
to do with his spirit than skills.
おそらく理屈より感覚的なものだろうな
それこそがプロの領域なんだ
That's the territory of pros.
For now, you only need to
remember that it can happen.
そういうものがあるって事を今覚えておけ
おーし 群馬へ帰るぞ
Alright, let's head back to Gunma.
健太
Kenta !
お前二号車の運転をしろ
You drive car #2.
Alright ! Let's get going !
おっしゃー
撤収
Sheesh, I can't drive the way I imagined.
やっぱイメージ通りいかねぇや
この頃タイヤが不思議な減り方をしてんだよな
The tires are wearing
out differently lately.
You must be trying something new.
おまえなんか新しいことやってるだろう
Yeah.
ああ この前のバトルで見せて貰った
I tried to copy this thing called one-hand
steering that I saw in a battle the other day.
ワンハンドステアっていうのを真似て見てるんだけど
That must be it.
そのせいかな
何だそれ
What's that ?
右手だけでハンドルを操作するんだ
You only steer with the right hand,
with your left hand on the gearshift.
左手はシフトレバー
おう
去年ガムテープデスマッチっていうのをやったんだけど
I had a race called a
duct-tape death match last year...
...and the technique seems similar.
そん時のテクニックに似てるといえば似てるかな
インプだとやり易いんだ
It's easy to do that with the Imp,
because it's got power-steering and 4WD...
パワステだし 4WDだから安定してるし
...so it's stable, and the
counter steering is minimized.
カウンタもちょっとで済むし
お前にしては上出来だな
Sounds impressive for coming out of
your mouth. The practice is actually useful.
いい練習だぞ それは
無駄なものを剃り落とせるかもな
You might be able to cut down the waste.
そんなもんかな よくわかんねぇけど
You think so ? I don't know
how that'd work, though.
If you can do the same with
the Eight-Six, that'll be great.
ハチロクでもできるようになれば大したもんだけどな
厳しいね それは
That's hard.
I can't do that, for now.
今んとこはまだ無理
You hit the top.
Your hands hurt, don't they ?
トップだよ 手が痛いでしょう
べっ 別に
N...not really.
嘘だー
Such a bad liar.
絶対今のは痛いはず 無理しちゃって
They must hurt.
You just won't admit it.
先から殆ど真面に飛んでかない
I haven't got a clean hit.
I didn't know it was so difficult.
こんなに難しいものだとは思わなかったよ
俺一休みするからお手本見せて
I'll take a break, so can
you demonstrate for me ?
えっ いいけど
I guess I can...
このアイアン自分のじゃなくてレンタルだし
But this iron isn't mine, it's a rental, so...
すげー 美佳って
Mika is incredible.
ゴルフの事は分からなくても 見ればわかる
I can tell, even if I don't
know anything about golf.
I saw the aura of a top-class player.
超一流のオーラがハッキリと見えた
電話出ませんよ 拓海のやつ
Takumi isn't answering his phone.
俺の勘だと 美佳ちゃんと会ってるな
I have a hunch that he's with Mika.
He chose a girl over his best friend ?
親友の電話より女をとるとは 許せない奴
It's unforgivable !
後せいばいしてくれるわ
I'll punish him later.
You thought he wouldn't ?
そりゃ当然だろう
In any case, Takumi and
Mika are suited to each other.
それにしても
拓海と美佳ちゃんはお似合いのカップルだと思うよ
それぞれ一芸に秀でた者同士で引かれ合うというか
Each has outstanding skills, so they
must be mutually attracted or sympathetic.
シンパシーを感じるんじゃないかな
遊んでないって言うか 擦れてない者同士で運命的な出会いなんだよ
It must be fate between a
dedicated and honest guy and girl.
Speaking of which,
I'm also dedicated and honest.
遊んでなくて 擦れてないって点では
俺も同じなんすけど
In other words,
talent makes the difference.
それはつまり才能の差ってことか
Did you really have fun playing golf ?
本当に面白かったの ゴルフなんて
I had a great time.
凄い楽しかったよ
美佳がボールを打つの見てるだけでも面白い
Just watching your
swing made me happy.
えっ ホント
Really ?
うん 凄いと思った
I thought you were incredible. I can tell.
分かるんだ 俺には
Thank you.
ありがとう
このごろちょっと自信無くすときもあるんだけどね
Although lately I've lost
my confidence at times...
いいや 自信持っていい
Oh, don't.
Just believe in yourself.
美佳は絶対超一流になれるよ
You'll become a top-notch player.
I hope so.
I want to become a pro.
だっといいな
あたし プロ目指してるんだ
A...actually, I do, too.
あっ あのさ
俺もなんだ
プロになるのが目標なんだ
My goal is to become a pro.
本当に 凄い
Really ?
That's awesome.
Then we should compete...
じゃ 競争だね
どっちが先に夢を実現させるか
...to see who makes their
dream come true first.
Team Spiral
Leader - Ikeda Ryuji (Zero)
Driver - Okuyama Hiroya (01)
いよいよ俺たちの出番ってわけか
So our turn has come, huh ?
笑っちまうけどな
This's almost like a joke.
246はともかく
246 was out of the question, but I thought
Katagiri's drivers had a solid chance.
カタギリの二人は鉄板だと思っていたが
プライドが高すぎるんだよ
They had too much pride, especially Minagawa.
特に皆川は
It can drag you down sometimes.
それが時には足を引っ張ることもあるんだ
You think you can win ?
お前は勝てるのか
Project D's Eight-Six is fast.
プロジェクトDのハチロクは速いぜ
俺は勝つよ
I'll win. I guarantee it.
百パーセントだ
There aren't any regulations,
so we can do anything, right ?
レギュレーションがないんだから 何でもありだろう
バカ正直にドラテクで勝負しようとするから足を掬われるんだ
If you try to compete in skills, you
could trip over your own naivety.
I had no intention of competing in
driving technique from the get-go.
俺は端からドラテクを競うつもりなんかない
I'll just try to win.
勝ちゃいいんだろう
You do understand.
分かってんじゃねか
ざわついた夏も終わりだ
This summer agitation will be over soon.
Hakone will quiet down.
これで箱根も少し静かになるさ
奥山の言うとおり
As Okuyama said, Minagawa must have
lost because he tried to save face as a pro.
皆川の敗因はプロとしての面子に拘ってからだろ
イコールコンディションである必要はない
There's no need for
conditions to be equal.
車のポテンシャルで 相手をねじふせてやればいい
We can beat our opponents
with superior vehicle potential.
いつの間に
When did he get there ?
どこのあほうか知らねーが
I don't know what kind of idiot he is,
but he's probably not one of the locals.
地元の車じゃねーだろう
この辺の奴ならスパイラルゼロと知って突っかかってくる奴はいねー
The locals wouldn't pick
a fight with Spiral's Zero.
思い知らせてやる
I'll show you what I've got.
この車のパワーについて来れるのか
It can keep up with my car's power ?
すげーなんだ今の
Wow, what was that ?
完全にバトルモードだったぞ
They were totally in battle mode.
先頭の赤いZはスパイラルのゼロか
The red Z in front must be
Spiral's Zero, but the rear...?
後ろの車はなんだった
速すぎてまったくわかんなかった
It was so fast that I couldn't see.
No, I know the car type
from its distinctive tail lights.
いや あの特徴のあるテールランプで車種は分かる
嫌な予感がする
I have a bad feeling.
まっ まさか あれか
You mean it's...?
離れない これだけのペースに付いて来るとは
He isn't falling behind.
It's amazing that he can
keep up with me at this pace.
こいつ ただ者じゃない
This guy's definitely no ordinary driver.
He doesn't miss the braking zone.
That means he knows this course.
ブレーキングポイントをきっちり押さえてくるあたり
コースを知ってやがる
If you're a local, who are you ?
地元なのか
誰だ てめー
ふざけんな
This is ridiculous.
何
What the...?!
くそ たれ
God dammit !
That was so close.
Someone else would've ended up dead.
間一髪
俺でなけりゃあの世行きだぜ
こんなまねをする奴は 俺の知る限りたった一人しかいない
As far as I know, there's only
one person who plays dirty like that.
間違いなく あいつが出やがった
No doubt, he's come.
ダークシルバーのR32
Dark silver R32, the Grim Reaper GT-R.
死神GTR
ここんとこ死神さんがチラホラ出没してるらしいですな
Apparently, the Grim Reaper has
been sighted a few times lately.
そうらしいな
So it seems.
He left home long ago, so
I don't know what he's been doing.
あいつはとっくの昔に家を出てるし
何をしてるのかも俺は知らない 興味もないしな
I'm not interested, either.
ただこれだけははっきりと言える
But I can tell you one thing for sure.
あいつの本当の標的は
His true target is Takahashi Ryosuke.
高橋涼介なんだ
So that's the "bitter fate" ?
因縁ちゅう奴ですな
He lost his girlfriend two years ago,
and he's been acting weird ever since.
二年前に恋人に死なれ
あいつがおかしくなったのはそれからさ
部屋に引きこもるようになり
He withdrew to his room, quit his job,
and stopped talking to the family.
仕事も辞めて 家族とも話さなくなった
How did Takahashi Ryosuke get involved, then ?
その話と高橋涼介は どこで繋がってくるんですかな
涼介も同じ女に惚れていたらしい
Apparently, Ryosuke had a
crush on the same chick.
Her name was...
女の名前は香織だったかな
...Kaori, I think.
これだけの高速コーナーでそれをやるってか
You had to do that in
this high-speed corner ?!
バカな女さ
She was foolish. Her suicide
screwed up the lives of the others.
自殺なんて仕上がるから
残された者たちの人生が狂うんだ
三人の間に何があったのか俺はそこまでは知らない
I don't know what
happened between them...
...it's been fate ever since
they met in med school.
大学の医学部時代からの因縁だからな
He's not the Grim Reaper himself...
あいつは死神何かじゃない
...he's just a pathetic guy who wanders around
because he's possessed by the Grim Reaper.
本当は 死神に取り付かれてさまよい歩くただの哀れな男だ
マジで 死ぬ気かもしれないぜ
He might be ready to die for real.
Incredible speed. Your speed is lethal.
なんつう速さだ
そのスピードはとんでもね凶器だぜ
それなりに荒っぽい対応をしないと
I'll have to play wildly, or I'll be finished.
俺も危ねか
ハラ立たしいが今日のところは降りる
It's frustrating, but I have to quit for today.
この借りは必ず返すぜ 死神
I'll pay you back later, Grim Reaper.
いよいよ今夜からだな
Project D's third round in
Kanagawa finally begins tonight.
プロジェクトDの神奈川第三ラウンド
社長に休みもらえなかったんで
The boss didn't give us any days off,
so we can't see the race this time.
今回も応援には行けないし
俺とイツキが土日丸々二日休むってのは
I guess both Itsuki and I trying to get
Saturday and Sunday off is too much to ask.
やっぱり無理あるかな
Project D is the enemy,
from Kanagawa's perspective.
神奈川サイドから見れば
プロジェクトDは敵なんだからさ
I wish we could send as many people
as possible to support the Gunma team.
少しでも群馬から送り込んでやりたいよな
This time around, I hear lots of guys
saying they'd go, despite the distance.
さすがに今回は遠くても行くって声をあちこちで聞くんが
Even so, we fellow Speed Stars members can't go. I don't know what to think of this.
それなのに 俺たちスピードスターズの仲間が行けないっていうのはどうなの
とりあえず 今日のところお前一人で行ってくれよ
For today, you should
just go by yourself.
あ いや それが
Well, actually, I'd love to...
そうしたいのは山々だけど
...but I'm kind of broke,
so I can't pay for the gas.
とりあえず金がないっつうか
交通費がね
なんだよ情けねーなもう
What the hell ?
You're pathetic.
俺 決めてるっす
I've decided.
次の最終戦は社長がなんと言おうと行かせてもらうっす
I'll watch the final race no
matter what the boss says.
イツキ
Itsuki...
I bet the best of Kanagawa will appear.
その時はきっと神奈川最強の相手が出てくるはずだし
勝っても負けても拓海一世一代の大勝負を
Whether Takumi wins or loses...
親友の俺が見届けないわけにはいかないっすから
...as his best friend, I must
see his race of a lifetime.
仕事首になっても構わないっす
I don't care if I get fired.
俺だけは行ってやらないといけない気がするんです
I feel like I have to be there.
But if he loses this time,
there won't be another one.
だけどさ 今回負けたら次はないんだぞ
負けないっす
He won't lose.
Takumi will never lose.
拓海は絶対に負けないっす
分かった 分かった
Okay, I got it, so don't cry, Itsuki.
I know how you feel.
泣くな イツキ
気持ちは分かるぞ
Itsuki is right.
We've got to see the final race.
イツキの言うとおりだよ
最終戦だけは行かないとな
何が何でも 見届けやりたいよ
We have to see the end, no matter what.
俺がチームリーダの池田竜次だ
I'm the team leader, Ikeda Ryuji.
Thanks for coming all the way here.
遠路はるばるようこそ
Nice to meet you.
I'm Takahashi Ryosuke of Project D.
よろしくお願いします
プロジェクトDの高橋涼介です
こっちの二人はうちのドライバーです
These are our drivers.
高橋啓介です
I'mTakahashi Keisuke.
I'm Fujiwara Takumi.
藤原拓海です
そうか あんたらがプロジェクトDか
So you guys are Project D.
あんたらに頼みというか 聞きたいことがある
I have a favor, or more
like a question to ask.
それぞれ思いつくまま答えてもらいたい
Just tell me what
pops into your head.
What is driving to you ?
走ることとはなんだ
さ 答えてくれ
Let me hear your answer.
Takahashi Keisuke, you go first.
まずは高橋啓介君 君からだ
In short, proof of masochism.
一言でいうなら マゾの証明
面白い
That's interesting.
How about you, Fujiwara ?
では藤原君は
俺にとっては 顔を洗うのと同じ日常です
To me, it's a daily activity,
like washing my face.
そりゃまた面白い
That's interesting, too.
And finally, you ?
最後に君だ
俺はドライバーじゃないけど 答えるべきかな
I'm not a driver here,
but should I answer ?
ぜひ 聞いてみたい
I'd love to hear it.
A dream.
夢
Okuyama didn't show up, after all.
結局顔見せませんでしたね 奥山さん
敵の出迎えをしてやる理由がないんだとさ
As he puts it, he can't find any
reason to greet his opponent.
それが あいつのモチベーションの上げ方ならそれもいいだろう
If that's how he raises
his motivation, that's fine.
そんなことより 坂本
Besides, Sakamoto, did you
sense anything from Project D ?
何か感じるか プロジェクトDに
ゾクッとするような存在感ですよ
Their presence gives me chills. It must
come from the momentum of continuous wins.
あれが勝ち続けている勢いってやつですかね
And yet, they aren't desperate,
or aggressive toward their opponent.
それでいて 気負ったところがまったくなくて
相手を威圧するような態度もない
落ち着き払っていて下手なプロよりもプロっぽいというか
They're so calm that they look
more pro than the real ones.
そうだろうな
I think you're right. Those three
are top-notch public street racers.
あの三人は超一流の公道ランナーだ
俺が日ごろから提唱するゼロの理論が試される最高の舞台だぜ
This is the perfect stage to test my
Zero theory, which I've been advocating.
The key is to free yourself from
destruction before you begin the race.
いかに心の雑念を振り払って戦いに望めるかが肝だ
無になることこそ理想的なドライビングスタイルだと
I believe that the ideal driving style can be
achieved through a mental state of zero noise.
俺は信じている
空気が湿ってますな
The air is moist, so it'll rain from dawn through
the day tomorrow, like the weather forecast said.
天気予報どおりあけ方から明日にかけては雨でしょうな
ウエットコンディションなら地元が有利かな
Wet conditions will probably benefit the
locals, because they know the course.
コースを知っているだけに
Generally, that would be true...
一般的にはそうでしょうが
...but Team Spiral tends to
rely on their cars' potential...
スパイラルっちゅうチームは
車の優位性にかける戦略ですから
雨はありがたくないのと違いますかな
...so they probably don't like rain.
私の予想では
I originally thought Project D's Eight-Six
driver would have a tough time if it was dry.
もしドライならばプロジェクトDのハチロクは苦しいと見ていました
奥山の車と比べて戦闘力に差がありすぎますからな
Compared to Okuyama's car, the
difference in performance is just too big.
しかし 雨となれば 互角
But in rain, it will equal out.
Plus, I can think of another
condition, besides the rain.
おまけに雨以外のもう一つ別の状況も考えられます
その場合 奥山ではプロジェクトDのボーヤには 勝てんでしょうな
In that case, Okuyama won't be
able to defeat Project D's lad.
Fujiwara Takumi:
Takahashi Ryosuke:
Takahashi Keisuke:
Uehara Mika:
Hojo Gou:
Kubo Eiji:
Ikeda Ryuji:
Minagawa Hideo:
Okuyama Hiroya:
Miki Shinichiro
Koyasu Takehito
Seki Tomokazu
Hayami Saori
Kiuchi Hidenobu
Kase Yasuyuki
Nakai Kazuya
Sakaguchi Shuhei
Takeuchi Itsuki:
Iketani Koichiro:
Kenji:
Fumihiro:
Kenta:
Fujiwara Bunta:
Iwata Mitsuo
Yao Kazuki
Takagi Wataru
Hosoi Hajime
Okano Kosuke
Ishizuka Unsho
Following the brake light of the front car.
Falling perfect lighten the focal
Kurai michi no saki ni bonyari nijimu akari
暗い道の先にぼんやりにじむ明かり
It's the silence like a silent film.
If the tires strike a silent wind
A
Central Anime
Production
Translation:
Hiro-kun
Timing:
Todd Perkins
Editing:
Lillian-Hime
Barbara
Todd Perkins
Brain
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Tayori ni naru mono wa sore shika mienakatta
頼りになるものはそれしか見えなかった
Kono namiki michi wo nukete ikeba kitto
この並木道を抜けていけばきっと
Tsukameru youna ki ga shita
つかめるような気がした
Get up! I just can't understand.
Give up! I just can't understand
Sokoniwa mada sagashimono wa nani mo nakute
外にはまだ捜し物は何もなくて
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
Yeah! It stops at this moment
Kono basho kara
この場所から
Please turn over the flyleaf.
Please stand alone on the flyleaf
I lost my way.
I lost my way
Shiroku kumotta mado to
白く曇った窓と的外れなNavigation
Mato hazure na navigation
Akaku kawatta shingou de
赤く変わった信号で
Side mirror ni utsuru shikai wo saegiru light
サイドミラーに映る視界を遮るLight
Tsumetai kaze ga hairikomanai youni
冷たい風が入り込まないように
Mado wo sotto shimetanda
窓をそっと締めたんだ
Get up! I just can't understand.
Give up! I just can't understand
Soko ni hirogaru michi wo erande susumu bokuwa
そこに広がる道を選んで進む僕は
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
Yeah! It stops at this moment
Kimi ga iru nana
君がいるなら
Please turn over the flyleaf.
Please stand alone on the flyleaf